Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪Let the daylight
pierce through the night♪
♪Unveiling the dazzling galaxy♪
♪This scorched remnant of myself♪
♪In this world of capricious tides♪
♪That perfect warmth♪
♪You are my only star♪
♪Heartless, obsessed, hopeful, loathing♪
♪How can we escape the regretful pasts♪
♪Watch the sky plunge into the sea♪
♪As dawn's first light
sketches the sky's outline♪
♪Entwined between our fingertips♪
♪When destiny weaves a brilliant net♪
♪Our souls are forged from the shards♪
=Flying Up Without Disturb=
=Episode 4=
Is that right?
This is going smoothly.
We'll complete it soon.
Divine artifact.
This is quite efficient.
- Of course.
- Pour more.
Pour it over all of these.
I bought this at the market
because I found it fun.
It's not medicine.
We shouldn't overuse it.
Then hurry and go
buy more.
This can save us.
Buy more?
That'd be perfect.
Why don't
you two
go to see
if there's more
available?
Well,
I can go by myself.
No need for company.
Really? That would be great.
This.
Open it yourself.
We need some other items.
Please buy them back,
okay?
That's easy.
Alright.
I'll go by myself.
Here, take it.
I'll take it.
Let go. I'll take it.
I'll help you.
I'll take it.
It hurts.
Did you do that on purpose?
I didn't.
Forget it.
Didn't expect
you to help me up.
I can get up myself.
Sir,
how much?
Two spirit stones.
That expensive?
Are you kidding me?
Are you an idiot?
You want to pay without bargaining?
Bargaining is troublesome.
What's troublesome about it?
I think
you'll get scammed
during traveling.
Watch me.
One spirit stone.
That's it.
W-Well...
One spirit stone?
Sell it or not.
If not,
we're leaving.
I do. I do.
See?
Easy, right?
I learned it.
Here.
I-I'm still mad at you.
Well...
(Five-Flavor Manor)
How long will this line take?
When will we reach the front?
What's sold here?
Why such a long queue?
This is the new shop
of Five-Flavor Manor.
Their pastries
are so delicious.
Indeed.
Buy some
for your loved one,
and she'll surely be delighted.
Loved one?
- He doesn't have one!
So you still don't
have a loved one.
Anyway, it is
none of your business.
Let's go.
You...
Can't you tell?
They are interested in you.
What's that to do with me?
What?
Forgot the lesson
taught by the Nascent Soul Elder?
If you really want pastries,
then get in line.
Don't talk to them.
Come here.
Still mad at me?
Senior Ling Hui.
I only realize now
that some people
can live such boring lives
and turn themselves
into a weapon,
toiling day after day.
Cultivation
is all about having fun.
There's so much
delicious food and fun in this world,
yet they don't enjoy any of it.
If they don't understand,
then their sect should
remind them.
Not like us.
Be careful. Watch your step.
Senior Ling Hui,
I consider him
a friend.
That's why I'm so worried.
See? I told you to be careful.
You didn't even try to drag me back.
You're sulking
and ignoring me.
Sir,
buy her an ice pop,
and she'll stop sulking.
Really?
Want one?
Want it?
Ice pop?
Considering
you bought me an ice pop,
I'll forgive you.
Why aren't you moving?
Watch out!
This time I dragged you back.
B-But
my ice pop fell on the ground.
I'll buy you another one.
Did you buy the spirit herbs?
Yes.
Local specialties?
You finished the ice pop.
So?
Go back.
Storybooks on sale.
(Jingxin Bookshop)
Today,
buy three books and get a discount.
Go take a look.
Don't miss out! Come here!
Come and see.
All great storybooks here!
Don't miss out!
Excuse me.
Take your time.
Fairy,
buy some storybooks?
Don't miss the sales.
Look.
(The Complete Works of Master Writer)
The complete works of Master Writer!
Sir,
you look familiar.
Last time you came here
and said to buy Master Writer's books.
Just asking.
See.
I specially stocked Master Writer's
complete works for you.
No need.
I was just asking.
You appreciate Master Writer too?
I was
just asking.
Oh my.
Can't believe you also appreciate him.
People who appreciate him
are quite rare.
Whatever.
I get it.
You're just feeling
a bit embarrassed,
right?
Don't be embarrassed
to be a fan of Master Writer.
Moreover, let me tell you.
Only ignorant people
would think his works
terrible.
Rest assured.
You have excellent taste.
And
it's normal for us
to have some preferences,
right?
Alright, let's just say I like him then.
Since you said so,
I must do something.
I'll buy
these books.
How much?
If you want them,
five spirit stones then.
Five spirit stones?
If that's too much,
three spirit stones.
Can't go any lower.
These are Master Writer's works.
Only cost three spirit stones?
Think the price is too low?
Then what do you think they're worth?
Certainly more than
three spirit stones.
Six spirit stones?
No! Way too low!
Ten?
Still low.
Fifty spirit stones.
That's about right.
Then they're yours.
Who reads
Master Writer's books nowadays?
Ten years ago,
he wrote Cultivation Record I,
which was utterly incomprehensible.
It's full of nonsense.
Exactly.
Watch your mouth!
A cracked pot goes with a cracked lid.
Every trash finds its owner.
Do you even understand his works?
We don't. You do.
Didn't you teach me to bargain?
Why did you set a higher price?
This is different.
These are Master Writer's books.
They're not worth fifty.
Of course, they are.
Master Writer's works
are priceless.
We can't let
others look down on him.
Fairy,
you have exceptional taste.
I haven't met
a customer with
elegant taste
like you in ages.
Here are your books.
(The Complete Works of Master Writer)
Okay.
The spirit stones you had
were spent on pastries.
Well...
Lady,
since you have no money,
why causing a scene here?
Exactly.
Thank you.
- See? She has money.
- Let's go.
See?
Weren't these supposed to be for me?
Why are you reading them first?
Don't be so stingy.
If you like them, take them all.
No need.
Actually, I have them all at home.
But mine
aren't as new as yours.
They've worn out.
In this case,
you read them before.
Then why read them now?
I can never read enough
Master Writer's books.
You really appreciate him?
Of course.
You too, right?
Well,
do you think Master Writer
is
a quiet person
who doesn't talk much?
Because
his works
are difficult to grasp,
yet the experiences
of his characters
aren't something
ordinary people would have.
Moreover,
each character
might seem cold in personality,
but in reality,
they're all righteous people,
who are eliminating evil
and upholding justice.
I've
wanted to be someone
like them ever since childhood.
Pity.
You can take action now.
I still have much to learn.
The characters from his works
are like...
Like you
Luanfeng Peak disciples,
being renown throughout
the entire Lingyou Realm.
Yet I...
I can't even properly use
my natal spiritual tool.
That's why my master
never let me venture out
and kept me stay in Yong City.
Come...
Come help me catch the ducks!
Lin Hu.
Why did you get all these ducks?
The village elders
told me
ducks can repel insects,
so I brought some over.
Come help me.
- Okay.
- Get in.
Got it.
Get in.
Hurry.
- Get in.
- Over there.
Over there.
Stop it.
Get in.
Huan Zong,
come help us.
Get these ducks in.
- Over here.
Over here.
Come here.
Huan Zong,
you're amazing.
This tea set
is the Nascent Soul Elder's?
Why did you steal
his tea set?
I brought it my own.
When traveling,
you carry a full tea set?
You don't get it.
Let me tell you.
Young Master has his own etiquette
for tea.
Take the tea leaves.
They must be
wrapped in handmade paper packets
and stored in lime jars.
The lime gets
replaced every ten days.
The brewing water
must be
the morning dew from pine needles.
And bring it to boil
with big heat,
then steep the leaves
in the boiling water.
That's it.
- So many details.
- Of course.
I thought
you Luanfeng Peak disciples...
What?
You thought us
to be barbaric and rude?
Well,
why hasn't the Master come out yet?
It's been ten days.
Did something
happen to him?
Should we
fetch a physician?
What for?
I'm the physician.
Master.
Did you figure it out?
Come with me.
Seek out the spirit herbs
listed on this prescription.
(Prescription)
Azure Phoenix Feather, Merfolk Scale,
Cloudseeker Twig.
For each herb obtained,
place it into
this specialized elixir furnace.
When all spirit herbs are gathered,
the furnace will produce
an elixir.
Take the elixir,
and your spiritual core
will fully recover.
Thank you, Master.
Master,
you are really amazing.
Do you like the specialty
from Yunhua Sect?
Also,
I've noticed many people sent
letters of gratitude
to physicians.
They'd hang those letters
right at the entrance.
It's so impressive.
How about
I prepare one for you?
Don't celebrate yet.
The spirit herbs
are extremely rare.
You'd better be mentally prepared
in advance.
If they're that rare, what should we do?
It's fine.
Master Song He
is an expert in medicinal herbs.
He'll certainly help me find them.
Thank you, Master.
And,
this laxative is for your master.
Laxative?
Master, seriously?
My master
has constant diarrhea.
Your master eats too much
and too diversely.
More excretion
will benefit him.
Alright.
Seclusion is exhausting.
Leave now.
Leave.
Azure Phoenix Feather, Merfolk Scale,
Cloudseeker Twig.
I've never even heard of these herbs.
How can we find them?
Huan Zong,
can your master
really find them all?
Perhaps let me
copy the prescription,
I'll review it.
Liuguang Sect is
the foremost sect in the world.
We'll find a solution.
But if
it's true,
why did you seek my help before?
I had no clues before,
but now I have the prescription.
Finding a solution
is merely a matter of time.
Rest assured.
Well, it's been ten days.
You should set off now.
I-I know.
I'll leave soon.
Then you go back soon
to find the herbs.
Okay.
But if you truly
encounter any difficulties,
send me a messaging talisman.
I'll help you out.
Here are my messaging talismans.
Where are yours?
Young Master never gives
his messenger talismans
to anyone.
By the way, Huan Zong,
you once promised
to grant me one request.
You haven't fulfilled it yet.
Just name it.
Well,
promise me not to overexert yourself
and take good care of yourself.
That's my request.
You too.
Well,
I'll take
my leave now.
Stop!
My fields are
all rice plants?
We were wrong.
Run!
We'll compensate you later.
Sorry, Master.
Stop!
Stop right there!
Sorry!
I planted Baichen Grass
in the fields before.
Where have you all taken them?
Senior Brother.
How is it?
Master Song He, any progress?
The elders and I have reviewed it.
Huang Qi is right.
This prescription
can indeed help
restore your spiritual core.
The Vermilion Grass,
Wuyuan Water and Wangqiu Stone
have already been located.
Thank you, Master Song He.
But the remaining six spirit herbs...
Just say it.
They are exceptionally rare.
However,
I've informed Master Hong Yan.
Though your injury
must remain secret,
he should
safeguard your ascension.
After careful consideration,
I decided to inform him.
More help means
better chances.
Rest assured.
I and the elders
will surely find a way to help you.
I wonder how Huan Zong is doing.
He hasn't sent
any messages to me.
Maybe
I'll message him.
My messenger talismans!
My messenger talismans.
What to do?
I can only
try my best.
Don't get damaged.
Or I couldn't contact
Huan Zong.
Why is the sun gone?
Let me blow on you.
I'll give you another blow.
Dry quickly, please.
Please.
Hang in there.
Let me try.
Why won't they activate?
Huan Zong.
They're all broken.
What should I do now?
Master.
What do you mean?
This command token
represents
leadership of the Liuguang Sect,
also your responsibilities.
It stays with you.
It...
Are you afraid...
I understand.
You concern about spiritual core,
and think about the big picture.
But we've dispatched disciples
to seek herbs for your
spiritual core.
Masters.
You got me wrong.
I think
I couldn't wait idly,
so I'll search for the herbs myself.
During my absence,
Luanfeng Peak affairs
will suffer.
After deliberation,
I decided to return the token
to your care.
When I recover,
I'll reclaim it then.
Young Master.
Masters.
Did your Young Master
mention his destination?
He...
H-He didn't...
He didn't mention it at all.
Report the situation to the head
and I every day.
Understood.
Take care of him.
Be cautious. Don't act rashly.
Yes.
Do you have sufficient funds?
We've brought ample travel funds.
Take this.
Don't be frugal.
Understood.
Right,
do you prepare the elixirs?
Yes.
Aside from the regular elixirs,
we also brought those
from Master Huang Qi.
These are new elixirs I made.
Understood.
And here are
my messenger talismans.
Yes.
Report
the situation to me
through these.
Yes.
And...
That's sufficient.
That's sufficient, Master.
If I don't go now,
Young Master will go afar
and I won't catch up with him.
Alright.
Go.
Yes.
Wait.
Remember my words.
Got it.
Young Master!
Wait for me, Young Master!
(Outside Qiu City)
Excuse me.
May I ask
how far Qiu City is from here?
Qiu City?
Thirty li ahead
lies Qiu City.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
(Then I'll)
(explore Lingyou Realm)
(The Complete Works of Master Writer)
(as written in Master Writer's storybooks.)
Qiu City belongs to Yunhua Sect.
Yunhua Sect
maintains regional stability
while granting autonomy
to local residents.
All Qiu City affairs
are handled by the city magistrate.
Due to proximity to western wilderness,
scavengers often
appear near Qiu City.
These scavengers are actually organized
petty thieves and pickpockets.
You!
Stop!
Return my purse!
Be careful.
Stop!
Give it back!
What happened?
Who is he? Just go.
Alright.
Just ignore that guy.
It's okay.
Young Master.
Are you thinking about
that Lady Kong Hou?
I've told you
if she considered you a friend,
she would've...
Where to?
Take a stroll.
Wait,
where to?
Where to exactly?
Stop!
Give back my purse!
Stop there!
Kong Hou.
Huan Zong.
The water isn't deep at all.
I thought...
Why are you here?
I was chasing someone...
Huan Zong.
Why are you here too?
Sorry.
I accidentally
pushed you into the water.
Let me help you.
I'll tidy you up.
Enough.
You suddenly
pushed me into water.
And you made my clothes
soaked.
I-I really didn't mean it.
Huan Zong.
Never thought
we'd meet again
in such a way.
Never expect it either.
Huan Zong.
I have matters to attend to.
Let's meet in Qiu City.
It's settled.
I won't stand you up, I promise.
You...
Are you kidding? A phoenix?
You've probably never seen a pheasant.
You!
I swear I'm telling the truth.
The genuine Azure Phoenix.
Azure Phoenix.
I heard the Zhaohan Sect people
are getting it to Qiu City.
(Azure Phoenix?)
(Isn't it what)
(Young Master is looking for?)
Really?
You're talking about the Azure Phoenix?
Watch out!
You thief!
Thank you for helping me.
Who are you?
I'm just
after the scavengers like you are.
I helped you
back there.
If I were evil,
would I have helped you?
Right?
(Seems like she's from a major sect.)
Don't worry.
We're both women.
I'll keep your secret.
If you dare blab,
I'll...
Your skills are impressive.
Clearly from a major sect.
And I'll
keep my promise.
So,
let's part ways here.
Go our separate paths.
(Fengxiang Inn)
What's wrong?
The Zhaohan Sect people are
escorting a phoenix from the North back
to the sect.
What's going on?
Why the commotion?
Why so many people?
Young Master.
That's what I told you,
the Zhaohan Sect's
Azure Phoenix.
Calm down.
We are so lucky.
Just find it right here.
Want to stand here
and do nothing?
Well,
should we take the suite or courtyard?
Your call.
Just somewhere quiet.
Fine.
You look
for her.
Me?
Any problem?
Not at all.
Then let's move.
Right,
I promised Huan Zong
to meet in Qiu City.
My stupid memory...
I'll definitely lose track of him again.
Lord will return soon.
If we prepare the elixir
from the Azure Phoenix,
and we'll be greatly rewarded.
You know
what to do.
Make it done.
Understood?
(Endless Visitors)
This way, please.
Be careful.
Our suites are
on these two floors.
Such a spacious courtyard.
This way, please.
Should you need an elixir chamber
or private courtyard,
we have them available.
A suite will do.
I can tell
you are from a major sect.
Why travel alone?
Without any attendant?
Cultivation
isn't about showing off.
No need
to scatter flowers
like some grand operas.
Well...
Look!
(Endless Visitors)
(Fairy Ling Bo, Zhaohan Sect)
It's her.
Fairy.
Watch your step.
Are you alright?
What a coincidence.
Fairy Ling Bo,
your disciples escorting the phoenix
have arrived.
Resting in suites.
This way.
Please.
(So she's from Zhaohan Sect.)
(How many flowers would be required)
(along her path?)
I intended to roam the martial world.
But upon seeing you,
I think I have to stop.
What do you want?
Lady,
got any fire?
Since you don't,
how did you manage
to ignite my heart?
M-Mind your words.
I could,
but upon seeing you,
at this moment,
I couldn't keep my composure.
Unctuous.
Lady,
to wash spiritual fruits,
what took you so long?
Come over here.
Lady.
You dare flirt with my maid?
Do you know who I am?
No.
I don't care.
Wait.
Flirting?
We're all roaming
in the martial world.
I simply wished to befriend her.
Besides,
I talked to your maid,
not you.
Why the anger?
Unless
you think
I ignored you
because I talked to your maid
instead of you?
Who cares?
Do you even deserve it?
So be it.
Why the anger?
I don't bother arguing with you.
Don't let me see you again.
I haven't finished
asking.
Never mind.
I'll do it myself tonight.
Didn't even name a specific spot.
Where should I look for Huan Zong?
♪Heaven and earth♪
♪As our cage♪
Who's singing at this hour?
♪Spring and autumn♪
♪Mortal dust♪
♪Being from nothingness♪
♪Ephemeral♪
♪Melancholy♪
No way.
What?
Why set a barrier here?
Waiter.
I demand a room change.
Who's lodging next to me?
Singing at this hour.
All rooms are occupied now.
Perhaps,
endure this one night?
Tomorrow morning,
I'll arrange it immediately.
I'll depart tomorrow.
Go negotiate on my behalf now.
Well...
Maybe you'd go yourself.
A barrier set at the door.
I can't get in.
Exactly.
Even you can't get in,
I couldn't possibly get in either.
So you won't go?
I...
Where's your room?
I'll sleep in your room tonight.
Don't.
Please don't.
Fairy, let me tell you.
The neighbor next door
is from the Zhaohan Sect.
That's a major sect.
I can't afford to offend them.
A major sect, so what?
I am
Kong Hou of Yunhua Sect.
Fairy,
to be honest with you,
the one living next to you
isn't human.
What?
Then a ghost?
No.
It's
the Azure Phoenix of Zhaohan Sect.
The phoenix can sing?
That's why
it's a millennia-old phoenix.
It's extremely precious.
I truly can't
afford to offend it.
If...
If you truly can't
make do,
then I
have to offer you
my room.
Forget it.
♪Flowing clouds, sleeves aflutter♪
♪Stars emerge above♪
♪Slanting sun, lingering glow♪
♪Grinding hues across the sky♪
♪Mountains, rivers, lakes, seas♪
♪Become my vessel♪
♪Chill spring breeze♪
♪Misty rain♪
♪This lifetime♪
So annoying!
I can't sleep,
and I can't even read in peace.
I'm about to lose my mind.
I can't take it.
I need to get some fresh air.
♪Looking back♪
He looks like
an immortal.
Huan Zong.
Huan Zong!
♪Roaming with the wind♪
♪Wandering about♪
♪A final ember of warmth abides♪
♪Absurd plots unfold♪
♪Mere spectators♪
♪Footprints left on shores♪
♪Fickle kisses burn♪
♪Withering in an instant♪
♪Lanterns glow, depicting her grace♪
♪Like rusted locks♪
♪Chaining our memories♪
♪Only scars remain♪
♪Breaking from worldly desires♪
♪Dreams shattered, but reality rolls on♪
♪Letting down my guard,
drowning in the perilous love♪
♪You stole my heart♪
♪Vows scatter with the air♪
♪All the wounds will heal with care♪
♪Love is mystery♪
♪So be it♪
♪She blazes uncontrolled♪
♪A sickness of the soul♪
♪Cold nights take their toll♪
♪So be it♪
♪All efforts go unrewarded♪
♪Breaking from worldly desires♪
♪Dreams shattered, but reality rolls on♪
♪Letting down my guard,
drowning in the perilous love♪
♪You stole my heart♪
♪Vows scatter with the air♪
♪All the wounds will heal with care♪
♪So be it♪